Not even the purest, most innocent eyes
Are spared the shadow of an ephemeral fate
The moon's shimmering light settles upon a house of cards,
A place entirely lost to silence
You will realize your foolish decision,
O lambs of the disdainful Lord
Dreams swelling with insanity surge forth,
Laying waste to that which is righteous
And now, should all reflected here be revealed as mere hypocritical deception,
Then the corpses of the victims shall speak unto you the truth
The New World will quicken as it awaits that moment
Peering into the abyss, through a chaining revelation
A sole glimmer of light reveals the truth:
An exquisite pain
All sneer at the treacherous who shield themselves,
And the ruthless who disguise themselves
The temple of vanity serves as the puppet's prison,
Its key warped into absurdity
You will realize that “those eyes,” though dignified,
Repeat the enigmatic and unceasing spiral
The trigger pulled through a defiled mind, the flock of decoys swallow it whole
I ask only that you search for the sole truth,
For it is undoubtedly tomorrow's long sought salvation
The New World will quicken as its slumber draws to a close
The hidden symbols beckoning the ruin to come
No matter how cruel the end,
You must face the truth with no hesitation
Should you choose, I will reveal unto you your destiny
An inescapable delusion, erosion, vanitas, lasting forevermore...
And now, should all reflected here be revealed as mere hypocritical deception,
Then the corpses of the victims shall take the shape of true love
The awaited moment will have arrived as the New World quickens
As it plunges to its demise through the echoing screams,
A sole glimmer of light reveals the truth:
A sinful life