Even as my tears spill, blown by the winds of our memories,
I’ll tread a new path, stopping for nothing
With a mind more clear than freshly fallen rain,
There’s a certain world that lies reflected, and there’s no place I can’t go
Within that white light, we raised our birth cries
And were blindfolded within a game of darkness and despair
I can write it now, wishing upon the swaying wind bell
Farewell, my dearly beloved– May you stay forever happy
You are me and I am you– You’re the product of my imagination
We’re best friends, now and forever, and I’ll never forget
With feelings more clear than the blue sky after rainfall,
There’s no need for telepathy any longer
You have my thanks, farewell
Within the blue flames, we awakened to our powers
Struggling side by side, we overcame our hardships
Within that white light, we raised our birth cries
And were blindfolded within a game of darkness and despair
I can write it now, wishing upon the swaying wind bell
Farewell, my dearly beloved– May you stay forever happy